STEFAN MARTIC

SENIOR FULL STACK DEVELOPER

CONTACT DETAILS

Address:

Novi Kneževac, Vojvodina, Serbia

Email:

stefan.martic.sm@gmail.com

Linked:

linkedin.com/in/stefan-martic

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF BELGRADEBachelor's Degree, Computer
Science

2008 - 2012

PROFILE

Accomplished full stack developer with strong experience in the development of web applications like SaaS, CRM, eCommerce, market places, FinTech platforms, etc based on JavaScript and PHP.

Have solid idea & knowledge of software development methodologies while being a proficient DevOps engineer who is familiar with the implementation of CI/CD based on Github/BB pipelines, Jenkins, Docker, etc.

- 1. Back-end development
- Node.js, Express.js, Loopback.io, NestJS
- Laravel, Symfony
- MongoDB, MySQL, PostgreSQL, Amazon DynamoDB
- 2. Front-end development
- React, NextJS, Gatsby, React Native
- Vue, Nuxt, Vuetify, Quasar
- Angular, AngularJS, Angular Material UI, Kendo UI, Ionic
- Tailwind, Boostrap, Bulma
- HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, Less, jQuery
- 3. DevOps
- CI/CD
- TDD
- Docker
- GitLab, Bitbucket Pipelines

WORK EXPERIENCE

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Self Employed | Jan 2018 - present

STEFAN MARTIC

SENIOR FULL STACK DEVELOPER

WORK EXPERIENCE

SENIOR FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Codeus | Aug 2016 - Dec 2017

- Implemented a responsive React website from scratch for a social media startup
- Built a React web app using hooks, Redux, best practices
- Constructed a REST and Socket API in Node.js (using the Express.js framework and Socket.IO library)
- Created an eCommerce website using NextJS and Contentful
- Built an eCommerce back-end using NestJS, integrated PostgreSQL and used TypeORM

*Technologies: React, Redux, Node.js, Express.js, Next.js, NestJS, PostgreSQL, TypeORM

SENIOR WEB DEVELOPER

ServalIT | Jan 2013 - Apr 2016

- Designed and created a knowledge management platform on a knowledge graph, utilizing a range of technologies, including Node.js, Typescript, React, and Mobx
- Developed 2+ full-stack web applications to analyze and process data for different clients
- Optimized the company's complaint handling process by creating and delivering highly efficient app-based solutions
- Developed and implemented a standalone data extraction "agent" and main-application features for a financial product based on Laravel & Vue.js

Skills: JavaScript, TypeScript, PHP, Laravel, Vue.js, React